chakri.com 2019-06-25

# Privacy policy

**Privacy Statement**

Chakri.com collects information about you and uses this information to help you connect with employers and job seekers and to provide other services to you. This policy describes how your information is collected and used and your choices with respect to your personal information.

**The Policy**

This policy applies to information we collect or use on sites and applications owned or controlled by Chakri.com.

Chakri.com is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of ad networks and other websites, third parties with whom we work to provide you personalized services, or those who access your information on our sites or applications.

**How we collect your information   **

We collect information about you when you use Chakri.com. We collect information directly from you such as your contact information, resume, and profile information. We also collect information about you automatically such as how you use and interact with Chakri.com, your demographic information, and information about your computer or mobile device.

**How we use your information**

We use the information we collect about you to deliver the products and services we offer, respond to you, and operate and improve our sites and applications. Our services include showing you personalized content and advertising on Chakri.com or other sites with which we have a business relationship. We may use your information to contact you about Chakri.com updates, conduct surveys, or to provide informational and service-related communications, including important security updates.

Information you share in public areas of Chakri.com or make visible in the resume and profile database may be accessed, used, and stored by others around the country. We strive to provide a safe environment by attempting to limit access to our database to legitimate users, but we cannot guarantee that unauthorized parties will not gain access. We also cannot control how authorized users store or transfer information you give to us, so you should not post sensitive information to Chakri.com.

**How we share your information**

We do not share contact information with third parties for their direct marketing purposes without your consent.

We share your information with third parties who help us deliver our products and services to you. These third parties may not use your information for any other purpose.

We may share information to third parties if you consent. For example, we may use your information to contact you about products or services available from Chakri.com or our affiliates. If you consent, we may supply your information to third parties who may contact you about their products or services. We may disclose to third parties information that we have collected from other websites.

We disclose information where legally required.

We may disclose and transfer information to a third party who acquires any or all of Chakri.com business units.

**How we store your information**

We store your information to make your interaction with Chakri.com more efficient, practical, and relevant. You may access, review, correct, update, or delete your resume or profile any time by [signing into your account](http://dev.chakri.com/login). If you do not have an account, please [contact us](http://dev.chakri.com/contact).

## About advertisements served Chakri.com

Chakri.com shows targeted job ads to you through our Career Ad Network. These ads appear on Chakri.com sites and on third party web sites. Targeted job advertising is based on your interests, which are inferred from certain demographic and geographic data and the search terms you enter when using Chakri.com and is not linked to your personally identifiable information without your permission.

### About advertisement served by Third Parties

Chakri.com allows third-parties to show you ads on Chakri.com. These companies can view, edit or set their own cookies and may use demographic, geographic, and behavioral information to show you targeted ads. To determine which targeted ads you see, we use third-party services to manage the behavioral, demographic, geographic and personal information we collect or gather about you. Chakri.com does not provide any personal information to the third party advertisers on our site unless you choose to allow it. Chakri.com has no control over, and is not responsible for, the practices of those third party advertisers. Chakri.com encourages you to visit their web sites and review their privacy policies.
